Finding Aid for the Anne Waldman Papers, 1945-2012
Anne Waldman Papers
- Handmade Books
  - Others
    - Berkson, Bill
      - Latest Works, April 2, 1974 (Box 74)
      - Quiet World, 1971 (Box 74)
      - Silver, November 27, 1970 (Box 74)
      - Telephone Message, 1971 (Box 74)
    - Berkson, Bill; Carroll, Jim; Fagin, Larry; Veitch, Tom. Things We'd Like to Do to Anne Waldman, April 2, 1970 (Box 74)
    - Berkson, Bill; Brownstein, Michael; Padgett, Ron. On cover: "Dear Michael, here are two of the Brenda Poems," February 18, 1969 (Box 74)
    - Berrigan, David; Berrigan, Kate; and Berrigan, Sandy. A Picture Book for Anne, undated (Box 74)
    - Berrigan, Ted
      - A Boke for Anne and Lewis on their Wedding, ca. 1967 (Box 74)
        (with contributions from many others)
      - How to Do a Sonnet etc., 1967 (Box 74)
      - A Little Birthday Bouquet for Anne, 1974 (Box 74)
      - Xmas Art Boke for Anne and Lewis, 1967 (Box 74)
    - Berrigan, Ted and Brainard, Joe. The Drunken Boat: photocopy of published work, 1974 (Box 74)
    - Berrigan, Ted; Brainard, Joe; Notley, Alice; Dine, Jim; et al.? Untitled. Folder of art and poetry for Anne Waldman and Michael Brownstein (cover and perhaps some of the artwork by Jim Dine), ca. 1970 (Box 74)
    - Black, Noel A. November to June, 2000 (Box 74)
    - Brainard, Joe
      - For You From Me, undated (Box 74)
      - 10 Mini-Essays for Anne With Love, Joe, Christmas 1972 (Box 74)
      - Some Train Notes, February 10, 1971 (Box 74)
      - Correspondence, Ron Padgett to Anne Waldman re gift of handmade books by Joe for Anne, May 30, 1994 (Box 74)
      - Purple book for Anne undated (Box 74)
    - Brainard, Joe and Hall, Steven. Love My Lover, A Valentine for Anne, undated (Box 74)
    - Brownstein, Michael. IS IT?, undated (Box 74)
    - Bye, Ambrose. A Day in the Life, 1993 (Box 74)
    - Bye, Reed
      - Anne's April 2 1979 Birthday Book, April 2, 1979 (Box 74)
      - April for Anne, 1981 (Box 74)
      - Birthday Book, "A Cottage Book," 1980 (Box 74)
      - 13 Favardin (Birthday in Teheran), 1982 (Box 74)
    - Clark, Tom
      - Crying in the Chapel, 1967 (Box 74)
      - Disappearing Usages, 1970 (Box 74)
    - Clark, Tom and Clark, Angelica. Xmas Book for Anne and Lewis from Tom and Angelica, 1968 (Box 74)
    - (Davis, Ken Angel), Spectrums: Watercolor, 2009 (Box 74)
    - Dunn, Douglas
      - A letter to Anne, undated (Box 74)
      - Alta Souvenir, July 20, 1979 (Box 74)
      - arms folded, 2009 (Box 74)
      - [Best Rest], September 1977 (Box 74)
      - This Little Book, 1977 (Box 74)
      - Untitled, cover "Anne," inscription "for Anne toward 1980. love, Doug," undated (Box 74)
      - Untitled, April 29, 1979 (Box 74)
    - Elmslie, Kenward and Brainard, Joe. The Baby Book: published work with art and other handmade additions, 1965, ca. 1980 (Box 75)
    - Evans, Curtis and Hundausen, Evan, eds. Anne Waldman Cereal: zine from Naropa Summer Writing Program, 2000 (Box 75)
    - Fagin, Larry, with photos by Rudy Burckhardt. Poems 1970, 1970 (Box 75)
    - Gatza, Geoffrey. A Poem: Fantasia Lights. Poem inside a small cigarrette box, undated (Box 75)
    - Hejinian, Lyn. The Unfollowed, 2011 (Box 75)
    - Holland, Joyce, ed. Matchbook: rare serial, No. E and H, undated (Box 75)
    - Hollo, Anselm and Hollo, Jane. Zoaire's Poem: handmade greeting card, 1995 (Box 75)
    - Hubbard, Elbert and Willis, Elizabeth. Little Journeys, 1998 (Box 75)
    - Kane, Daniel; Kane, Gillian and Wakefield, Stacy. All the Aldas, August 08, 2002 (Box 75)
    - Kite, Mary. Tyro, March 24, 2006 (Box 75)
    - Michaelis, Catherine. May Day Customs and Beliefs, 2002 (Box 75)
    - Notley, Alice. Anne, 1974 (Box 75)
    - Padgett, Ron
      - An Adventures in Poetry Pirate Edition, 1972 (Box 75)
      - True Facts from Nature: For Anne, April 1974 (Box 75)
      - wishing you a good year, April 1971 (Box 75)
    - Ricard, Rene. The Rose Without Thorns (in metal box, along with photograph of Bill Berkson in 19th-century attire), undated (Box 75)
    - Scalapino, Leslie; Estrin, Jerry; Davies, Alan; Moriarty, Laura; Cole, Norma; Howe, Fanny. War: limited edition publication, O Books, "0/3," ca. 1991-1993 (Box 75)
    - Schelling, Andrew
      - Right in the Pocket, December, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Winter Solstice Poems 1991-1992 (Box 75)
      - Dates in December: A Valentine for Anne, February 1996 (Box 75)
      - Six Haibun for The Turning Seasons 2000 (Box 75)
    - Schiff, Harris. Secret Clouds: original typed manuscript edition later published by Angel Hair Books, 1969 (Box 75)
    - Schjeldahl, Peter. Think About That!, undated (Box 75)
    - Searls, Damion. A History of Printing in America, 2003 (Box 75)
    - Sikelianos, Eleni and Hunt, Laird. L &E, September 03, 2000 (Box 75)
    - Ulmer, Spring. Older than Trains, undated (Box 75)
    - Warsh, Lewis
      - Life After Death, 1971 (Box 75)
      - The Little Red Book #4, September 1996 (Box 75)
      - Stash, 1970 (Box 75)
      - Targets, April 2, 1971 (Box 75)
      - True Colors, 1970 (Box 75)
      - Warsh, Lewis, with contributions from Dennis, Donna; Lesser, Eugene; Snyder, Gary; Creeley, Robert; et al.? Birthday Book, 1970 (Box 75)
    - Wille, Andrew. See Also and Look at Him. Miniature book, 2006 (Box 75)
    - Yates, Katie. Is It Happening: limited run publication, BOOG Literature, 1992 (Box 75)
    - Naropa print workshop and letter press class projects (6 folders), 1999 (Box 75)
    - Unidentified. MA TA FA UA, undated (Box 75)
    - Untitled: scrapbook for Anne Waldman, started for her birthday with contributions from various friends, ca. 1970-1972 (Box 76)
- Printed Material
  The Printed Material series (4 linear feet, 1 oversize box, 1 portfolio) encompasses the subseries Broadsides; Posters, Flyers, and Programs; and Clippings.
  Broadsides are broken down into those by Anne Waldman, Collaborations (between Waldman and others), and Others--that is, works by others. Material in the Posters, Flyers, and Programs subseries is for the most part grouped chronologically. Separate, topical divisions have been made for undated material. Clippings are arranged in rough chronological order by decade, where date is known.
  - Broadsides
    - Anne Waldman (Box 77)
    - Collaborations (Box 77)
    - Others
      - A-L (Box 77)
      - M-Z and unidentified (Box 77)
    - Postcards and Bookmarks (Box 77)
    - Card game/sayings (Box 77)
  - Posters, Flyers, and Programs
    - 1960s (2 folders) (Box 77)
    - 1970s
      - 1970-1971 (Box 77)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 77)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 77)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 77)
      - 1979 (Box 77)
      - c. 1960s/1970s (Box 77)
    - 1980s
      - 1980-1981 (Box 77)
      - 1982-1984 (Box 77)
      - 1985-1989 (Box 77)
      - c.1980s (Box 77)
    - 1990s
      - 1990-1991 (Box 77)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 77)
      - 1994-1999 (Box 78)
      - c.1990s (Box 78)
    - 2000s (7 folders) (Box 78)
    - Material (by topic) Undated
      - Book publication announcements (Box 78)
      - Boulder (includes Naropa) (Box 78)
      - Buddhist-related (Box 78)
      - City Lights, undated (Box 78)
      - Douglas Dunn, undated (Box 78)
      - Giorno Poetry Systems, ca. 1978-? (Box 78)
      - 98 Greene St. Loft, NY (Box 78)
      - The Poetry Project at St. Mark's, undated (Box 78)
      - Postcards: artist exhibition announcements, etc. (Box 78)
      - Miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 78)
    - Book Presses: catalogs, publicity, etc.
      - City Lights Books, 1975-1997 (Box 78)
      - New York State Small Press Association, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
      - Toothpaste Press/Coffee House Press, 1979-2002 (Box 78)
      - Z Press, Kenward Elmslie, 1977-1980, undated (Box 79)
      - Other
        - A-L (Box 79)
        - M-Z (Box 79)
    - Newsletters
      - 1970s (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1980s (Box 79)
      - 1990s (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - 2000s (3 folders) (Box 79)
      - Folklore Center, 1966-1968 (Box 79)
      - Quadrille: Bennington College alumni newsletter, 1969-1976 (Box 79)
  - Clippings
    - 1960s (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - 1970s (15 folders) (Box 79)
    - 1970s (3 of 15 folders) (Box 80)
    - 1980s (12 folders) (Box 80)
    - 1990s (6 folders) (Box 80)
    - 2000s (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - Undated (3 folders) (Box 80)
    - Miscellaneous articles and printouts (3 folders) (Box 80)
- Art
  (stored in boxes 81, 82, 99-108, and one portfolio; grouped by size and/or medium)
  Art (1 linear foot, 10 oversize boxes, and 1 portfolio) is made up of artworks by Waldman and her family and friends, as well as various pieces she has collected over the years. Work in many different media exists, including prints, paintings, sketches, drawings, and collages.
  - Baumann, Verena. Untitled watercolor. "Painting by Swiss artist Verena Baumann at George Schneeman's funeral." New York City, 2009 (Box 81)
  - Beltrametti, Franco. portraits de trobairitz, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Berrigan, Ted. Hi folks: ballpoint pen (Box 81)
  - Blatter, Wolf Dietrich. 2 photo collages, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Brainard, Joe
    - Poems [heart drawing]: collage & mixed media, Valentine's Day 1978 (Box 81)
    - "Sigh": pen & ink drawing, undated (Box 81)
      (cover art?)
    - Drawing of a cherry: pen (Box 81)
  - Brownstein, Michael. "Is Being Forged": drawing, felt tip pen (Box 81)
  - Bye, Reed? [Anne Waldman's guess]. 2 watercolors (Box 81)
  - Cole, Norma. "Porno Murder: We Poetry": photocopy, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Copp, Fletcher. Artist Hero Series: Giotto, collage, 1977 (Box 81)
  - Dunn, Douglas.
    - Appropriation of Red Grooms catalog, 1976 (Box 81)
    - Here's a piece of my ceiling: collage, mixed media, undated (Box 81)
  - Elovich, Richard (secretary to William S. Burroughs). Collage, undated (Box 81)
  - Fagin, Larry. "When I think of the thought machines I whistle softly to myself": collage, 1973 (Box 81)
  - Gross, Mimi
    - Three portrait sketches of Anselm Berrigan, undated (Box 81)
    - Dharamsala, India, copies of sketches 2008 (Box 81)
  - Guttman, Kaitlyn. "Third Mind" workshop booklet cover: collage, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Jacquette, Yvonne. "To Anne (Xerox print)": photocopy, undated (Box 81)
  - Kearney, Tapa. Ridiculous Interiors: photo collage (Box 81)
  - Notley, Alice and Oliver, Doug. Watercolor card and letter (Box 81)
  - Pittore, Carlo. Stamp art, photocopies of sketches, flyer, 1986, undated (Box 81)
  - Smith, Jesse (Patti Smith's daughter). Card decorated with chewing gum sticks, 2000 (Box 81)
  - Smith, Patti. First line reads "devotions. to Arthur Rimbaud": print, #20, undated (Box 81)
  - Trungpa, Chogyam, Rinpoche. Calligraphy, undated (Box 81)
  - Waldman, Anne
    - "'Birthday Collage' for DADDY," collage on cardboard, 1978 (Box 81)
    - "Hand of the Poet": handprint, undated (Box 81)
    - "pearl of red ceiling": collage, undated (Box 81)
    - "Self Portrait," ca. 1973 (Box 81)
    - Drawing with caption "TV Sleep," undated (Box 81)
    - Footprint, undated (Box 81)
    - Landscape: drawing, 1969 (Box 81)
    - Original cover for limited edition of So Help Me Sappho: collage, undated (Box 81)
    - Cutout collages (2 folders), ca. 1966 (Box 81)
    - Birthday collage and poem for Reed Bye, 1980 (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Waldman, Anne and Clark, Tom. Miscellaneous drawings and writings, undated (Box 81)
  - Waldman, Anne and Englebardt, Jill. copy of painting with writing on cardstock, undated (Box 81)
  - Waldman, Anne and Giorno, John. Poem on construction paper, April 17, 1971 (Box 81)
  - Waldman, Anne; Bye, Reed; Bye, Ambrose; Hawkins, Bobbie Louise; et al.? Exquisite corpse drawings and poems (2 folders), ca. 1980s (Box 81)
  - Wilkie, Britton, "For 'In April '--3 illustrations": pen & ink drawings and pencil sketch of Anne Waldman, undated (Box 81)
  - Various authors and unidentified. Reproductions: Jacquette, Yvonne; Stanton, Susan; Freilicher, Jane; Baxter, Glen; Waldman, Anne; and unidentified. Mimeographs and photocopies of sketches and drawings (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991, undated (Box 81)
  - Unidentified
    - G______? [illegible], Ann. [possibly Ann Lauterbach?] "Crack in the World": color drawing (cover?) with wax additions, 1987 (Box 81)
    - L___? [illegible]. Birthday card for Anne: drawing, undated (Box 81)
    - _____?, Angela and _____?, Ebbe [last names not given]. Wedding invitation, "Angela and Ebbe": felt tip pen, undated (Box 81)
    - [Schneeman, George?] Hi Anne: pen & ink drawing (Box 81)
    - "So are you!": photograph with text, undated (Box 81)
    - Painting: red flowers, undated (Box 81)
    - Skeleton print, undated (Box 81)
    - Collage, undated (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous drawings (includes drawings possibly by Joe Brainard and George Schneeman), (2 folders), 1970, undated (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous watercolors, undated (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous art in silk folder, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil painting. Rene WW?, 1967 (Box 82)
- Photographs, Slides, and Negatives
  The Photographs, Slides and Negatives series consists of approximately 2.5 linear feet of photographic materials documenting a variety of subjects, including Waldman's childhood and school years, her large circle of friends and colleagues, and her publishing and performance activities.
  - Photographs
    - Personal
      - Family and childhood, 1946-1976, undated (Box 83)
      - High school and college, 1959-1963, undated (Box 83)
      - Anne Waldman snapshots and informal photographs, 1969-1982, undated (Box 83)
      - Friends and colleagues (6 folders), 1966-1997, undated, 6.0 folders (Box 83)
      - Artwork, 1987, undated (Box 83)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 1970-2003, undated (Box 83)
    - Professional
      - Naropa Institute, 1982-1998, undated (Box 83)
      - Performances and speaking engagements (5 folders), 1969-1996, undated (Box 83)
      - Performances by others (Box 83)
      - Allen Ginsberg, undated (Box 83)
      - Lawrence Ferlinghetti and John Giorno, 1998 (Box 83)
      - Douglas Dunn, 1975-1976, undated (Box 83)
      - Portraits (4 folders), 1966-1991, undated (Box 83)
      - Publishing and book cover photographs
        - Baby Breakdown, 1968 (Box 83)
        - No Hassles, 1971 (Box 83)
        - First Baby Poems, 1983 (Box 83)
        - Identikit (Jim Brody), undated (Box 83)
        - Photograph of Cesar Moro for Frances Waldman book of translations, undated (Box 83)
      - Rolling Thunder Revue, 1976 (Box 83)
      - St. Mark's Poetry Project, 1968-1997 (Box 83)
      - Schule für Dichtung in Wien, 1992-1994 (Box 83)
  - Slides and Negatives
    - Performances, undated (Box 84)
    - Personal
      - Jerry Hiler photographs of Ambrose Bye on 5th Avenue, New York, 1983 (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous negatives, undated (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous slides, undated (Box 84)
  - Albums and Scrapbooks
    - Album (includes travel to Egypt and Greece), ca. 1963 (Box 84)
    - Hand-bound scrapbook (includes photos of Anne Waldman, Lewis Warsh, Waldman/Warsh Wedding, Ted Berrigan, Tom Clark, Lee Harwood, Jonathan Cott, Martha Rockwell and others), ca. 1966-1967 (Box 84)
    - Album, (includes photos of Anne Waldman, Lewis Warsh, Joe Brainard, Michael Brownstein, others) 1960s (Box 84)
    - Scrapbook (includes photos of Ted Berrigan, Lewis Warsh, Tom and Angelica Clark, Kenward Elmslie, Joe Brainard, Michael Brownstein, Bill Berkson, Lewis MacAdams, and others), ca. 1970-1971 (Box 84)
    - Album (includes photo of Anne Waldman, Michael Brownstein, Ron Padgett, Dick Gallup, Nick Dorsky), ca. early 1970s (Box 84)
- Audiovisual
  The Audiovisual Series has been divided into four subseries: Sound Recordings, Video Tapes, DVDs, and Digital Files. The series provides a unique perspective on Waldman's activities, and thus complements and expands the manuscript and photographic holdings. Including recordings of readings, lectures, and interviews given by Waldman and others, the series strongly represents the sounds and voices of late 20th century American poetry.
  - Sound Recordings
    - LPs and 45s
      - (WALDPHON-1) "John Giorno and Anne Waldman" (Giorno Poetry Systems, GPS-010-011), 1977, 12 inch, 33 rpm) (Box 85)
      - (WALDPHON-2, WALDPHON-3 and WALDPHON-4) Anne Waldman, "Uh-Oh Plutonium" (Hyacinth Girls Music, HG 001), 1982, 3.0 copies; 7 inch, 45 rpm) (Box 85)
      - (WALDPHON-5) Labeled "Anne Waldman and Michael Brownstein," undated, 6 inch, 45 rpm "voice-o-graph" recording) (Box 85)
      - (WALDPHON-6) Bob Dylan "George Jackson," labeled "given to me by Bob Dylan, November 1971" (Columbia, 4-45516), 1971, 7 inch, 45 rpm) (Box 85)
    - Reels
      (Open reel tapes have been reformatted to compact disc. Request corresponding CD-R copies WALDCDR-1 through WALDCDR-9.)
      - (WALDRR-1)"Channel 13 program on Frank O'Hara and Ed Sanders" (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-1), 1966, 7 inch reel, 3 ¾ ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-2) "Anne Waldman recording for Architectural League Event" (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-2), 1968, 5 inch reel, ? ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-3) "Brain/Baby: The Poetries of Michael Brownstein and Anne Waldman (KPFA-FM Radio, Berkeley, CA) (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-3), 1971, 10 inch reel, ? ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-4) Anne Waldman poetry reading on WUOM, Ann Arbor (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-4), 1971, 7 inch reel, 3 ¾ ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-5) Anne Waldman "Fast Speaking Woman" (S Press Tapes, no. 55) (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-5), 1977, 5 inch reel, ? ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-6) "Anne Waldman Musical Garden" (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-6), 1988, 5 inch reel, 15 ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-7) "Anne Waldman England Drama" (includes Lady Anne's speech from Richard III, Act I, Scene II, and Solange from the Maids by Jean Genet) (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-7), undated, 5 inch reel, ? ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-8) "Ann Waldman" (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-8), undated, 7 inch reel, 15 ips (Box 85)
      - (WALDRR-9) Unidentified reel (CD access copy available as WALDCDR-9), undated, 7 inch Reel, ? ips (Box 85)
    - Compact Discs
      - (WALDCD-1 and WALDCD-2) "Anne Waldman, Recorded Live in Amsterdam 6-2-91": includes wood case and booklet (Soyo Records), 1991, 2.0 copies (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-3) Anne Waldman, "Alchemical Elegy: Selected Songs and Writings" (Fast Speaking Music), 2001 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-4) Anne Waldman, Romantic Poems, undated (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-5) Allen Ginsberg, interviewed by Jack Foley, KPFA, October 4, 1996 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-6) Anne Waldman and Andrew Schelling, "Northwestern Exposure", the Legacy of Allen Ginsberg, April 22, 2001 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-7) Anne Waldman with Paul Nelson, "Northwestern Exposure", Oppositional Poetics, May 11, 2002 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-8 and WALDCD-9) Bob Dylan Tribute, Town Hall, May 19, 2001 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-10) Anne Waldman, "Battery," December 17, 2002 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-11) Anne Waldman and Cecelia Woloch, MFA Poetry Reading, January 6, 2003 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-12) "Anne Waldman, Rhizomic & Radical Poetics," January 7, 2003 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-13) New England College MFA Poetry Program, MPE Audio Compilation, Faculty and Student Lectures, January 2007 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-14 and WALDCD-15) Anne Waldman at Buffalo State University, April 13, 2007 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-16) Anne Waldman & C. Fitz, Bowery Poetry Club, New York City, April 20, 2007 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-17) Prague Writers Festival, 2001 Nights: The Art of Storytelling, Laterna Magika Theatre, June 7-11 2009 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-18) Anne Waldman, Romantic Poems, undated (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-19) Going Vocal, the Jack Kerouac School of Disembodied Poetics, 2011 (Box 85)
      - (WALDCD-20) Anne Waldman, SWP, Class #1, undated (Box 85)
    - Cassettes
      (Cassettes have been reformatted to compact disc. Request CD-R in corresponding WALDCA-R- number.)
      - Readings
        - Anne Waldman
          - (WALDCA-1) "Memorial Day" with Ted Berrigan, St. Marks Church In-The-Bowery (CD access copy available), May 5, 1971 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-2) Cherry Valley Labor Day Reading with Michael Brownstein, Charley Plymell, John Giorno, Ray Bremser, Michael Andre, Susan Quist, Cherry Valley, NY (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), 1974 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-3) "Dawn of Tantra," poetry reading with Diane di Prima, and Allen Ginsberg, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 30, 1974, 2.0 cassettes (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-4) "Dawn of Tantra," poetry reading with Diane di Prima, and Allen Ginsberg, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 30, 1974 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-5) "Potpourri of Poetry" with Allen Ginsberg, Chogyam Trungpa, Ted Berrigan, Diane di Prima, Philip Whalen, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available), Summer 1975 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-6) Poetry Reading with Allen Ginsberg and Michael Brownstein, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), April 2, 1976, 2.0 cassettes (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-7) Poetry Reading with Allen Ginsberg and Michael Brownstein, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), April 2, 1976 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-8) "Anne Waldman: Chants and Poems" (CD access copy available), August 1, 1976 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-9) Poetry Reading with Allen Ginsberg (CD access copy available), August 3, 1977 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-10 ) Reading with Reed Bye, Michael Kohler, Germany (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), February 16, 1978 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-11) Reading (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), November 11, 1978 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-12) Reading with Gary Snyder, University of Texas at Austin (CD access copy available), April 19, 1979, 2.0 cassettes (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-13) Reading with Gary Snyder, University of Texas at Austin (CD access copy available), April 19, 1979 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-14) Anne Waldman, Swarthmore College (CD access copy available), March 16, 1980, 2.0 cassettes (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-15) Anne Waldman, Swarthmore College (CD access copy available), March 16, 1980 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-16) Poetry reading with Clark Coolidge and Dick Gallup, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 2, 1980 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-17) Anne Waldman, Harbor Front (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 24, 1984 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-18) Anne Waldman, San Francisco Art Institute (CD access copy available - 2CDs), July 9, 1985 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-19) Reading with Allen Ginsberg, Stephen Taylor (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 10, 1985 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-20) Naropa Summer Series reading, July 1985 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-21) Performance (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 16, 1987 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-22) Performance with Susan Edwards (CD access copy available), October 7, 1987 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-23) Performance, Lawrence (KS?) (CD access copy available), 1987 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-24) Joel Oppenheimer memorial reading (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), February 2, 1989 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-25) Reading with Allen Ginsberg, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 25, 1989, 2.0 cassettes (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-26) Reading with Allen Ginsberg, Naropa Institute (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), July 8, 1989 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-27) Reading with Jerome Washington, Penny Lane, Boulder Colorado (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), October 2, 1989 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-28) Reading at QE2, Albany, NY (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), October 7, 1989 (Box 86)
          - (WALDCA-29) Reading and question and answer session at "CHS," (CD access copy available - 2 CDs), December 12, 1990 (Box 86)